A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records of the JDR 3rd Fund, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1989; 1
    - Director's Office, 1955, 1957-1989; 3
      - Asian Individuals, 1955, 1957, 1959-1983; 4
        - T, 1961, 1964-1980
          - Takeyama, Minoru, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 1420)
          - Talalla, Ida, 1969, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1421)
          - Tam, Bui Duy, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 1422)
          - Tamura, Mimi, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1423)
          - Tan, Sylvia S. H., 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 1424)
          - Tan, Teng-Kee, 1974-1978 (Box 42, Folder 1425)
          - Tan, Teong Eng, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1426)
          - Tanaka, Massaki, 1964-1968, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1427)
          - Tandavanij, Suchawadee, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1428)
          - Tandavanij, Suchawadee, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1428A)
          - Tandon, B. N., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1429)
          - Tang, Cho Tung, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1430)
          - Tange, Kenzo, 1965-1968, 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1431)
          - Tangri, Manjeet K., 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1432)
          - Tangri, Manjeet K., 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1432A)
          - Tank, Vajubhai M., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1433)
          - Tantisuk, Sawasdi, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1434)
          - Tantoco, Rosario, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1435)
          - Tao, Grace, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 1436)
          - Tarapor, Mahrukh, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 1437)
          - Teng, Chuah Thean, 1964-1968 (Box 42, Folder 1438)
          - Teng, Chuah Thean, 1964-1968 (Box 247, Folder 4713)
          - Teng, K. Seng, 1971-1972, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1439)
          - Teng, Mee Huong, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1440)
          - Teo, Chin Chye, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1441)
          - Teo, Chin Chye, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1441A)
          - Teoh, Kit-Fong, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1442)
          - Terrayama, Shoji, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1443)
          - Teshigahara, Hiroshi, 1970-1972 (Box 43, Folder 1444)
          - Teshigahara, Sofu, 1964, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 1445)
          - Thaivej, Vivat, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1446)
          - Thaker, Madhusudan V., 1970-1976 (Box 43, Folder 1447)
          - Thakkar, Sudha, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1448)
          - Thakurdsai, S. G. (T'Desai), 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 1449)
          - Than, U Htut, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 1450)
          - Thanangadan, Thomas G., 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1451)
          - Thapar, M. M., 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1452)
          - Tho, Nguyen van, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1453)
          - Thondup Narkyid, Ngawang, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 1454)
          - Thongthew. Somchintana, 1966, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1455)
          - Thongthew, Somchintana, 1966, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1455A)
          - Tjiong, W. P., 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1456)
          - Tjui, Maria, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1457)
          - Toda, Teisuke, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1458)
          - Togi, Masatoro, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1459)
          - Toishi, Kenzo, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 1460)
          - Tomiyama, Hideo, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1461)
          - Tong, Suit Chee, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1462)
          - Tong, Tew Nai, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1463)
          - Tono, Yoshiaki, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 1464)
          - Topgyal, Penpa, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1465)
          - Torii, Kazuyo, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 1466)
          - Torres, Emmanuel, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 1467)
          - Tow, Theow-Huang, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1468)
          - Toyoshima, Soroku (Box 43, Folder 1469)
          - Tran, Hai-Linh, 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 1470)
          - Tran, Nghiem Cong, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1471)
          - Trinh, Bran, 1961, 1967, 1976, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1472)
          - Trinidad, Florinda, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 1473)
          - Trivedi, Shiva Dayal, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 1474)
          - Trungpa, Chogyam, 1972-1973, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1475)
          - Tsang, Brian H. K., 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1476)
          - Tsao, Lionel, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 1477)
          - Tse, Edward C., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1478)
          - Tseng, Pei-Yao, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1479)
          - Tsering, Yanki, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1480)
          - Tsering, Yanki, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1480A)
          - Tsong, Fou, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1481)
          - Tsou, Hsiao-Liang, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1482)
          - Tsuai, Margarate, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1483)
          - Tsubonoh, Katsuhiro, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1484)
          - Tsuji, Nobuo, 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1485)
          - Tulku, Doboom, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1486)
        - U, 1968-1974, 1978, 1980-1981
          - Uchiyama, Ayako, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 1487)
          - Ueda, Nobuya, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 1488)
          - Uematsu, Kieji, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1489)
          - Uenami, Wataru, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 1490)
          - Ung, Seng-Ny, 1974, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1491)
          - Ungphakorn, Puey, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1492)
          - Unnithan, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 1493)
          - Upadhyaya, Om, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1494)
          - Ursani, Aslam, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1495)
          - Usami, Keiji, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1496)
          - Utaco, Yoji (Box 44, Folder 1497)
        - V, 1964, 1966-1980
          - Vaidya, Ramesh, 1975, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 1498)
          - Vakil, Zenobia, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1499)
          - Van, Sieng, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1500)
          - Varadarajan, Muthusamy, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 1501)
          - Varavarn, Kasama, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1502)
          - Varavarn, M, R, Chanvudhi, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1503)
          - Varma, G. Kumara, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 1504)
          - Varma, K. M., 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1505)
          - Varma, P. L., 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1506)
          - Varma, Rommel, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1507)
          - Vasant, Suresh, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 1508)
          - Vasudeo, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1509)
          - Vaz, Joe F., 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1510)
          - Veng, Long & Hy Khauv Say, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1511)
          - Venkatroman, N. V., 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1512)
          - Verma, Anil, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 1513)
          - Verma, Ashok K., 1969, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1514)
          - Verma, Priyamwada, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1515)
          - Verma, Priyamwada, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1515A)
          - Victoria, Pablo, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 1516)
          - Villa, Jose Garcia, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1517)
          - Vishvapriya, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 1518)
          - Vishwanathan, Rama, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 1519)
          - Vitug, Romeo V., 1970 (Box 44, Folder 1520)
          - Voi, Mali, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 1521)
          - Vyas, H. Kumar, 1964, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 1522)
          - Vye, Mike, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 1523)
        - W, 1966-1982
          - Wad, A. Bal, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 1524)
          - Wadia, Coomi N., 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1525)
          - Wakabayashi, Lynn, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 1526)
          - Wakankar, Vishnu S., 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1527)
          - Wakayama, Yoshiko, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1528)
          - Wakita, Aijiro, 1968-1970 (Box 45, Folder 1529)
          - Wang, Been Zen, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1530)
          - Wang, Charles Y., 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1531)
          - Wang, Chi-wu, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 1532)
          - Wang, Chung-Ho, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1533)
          - Wang, Eugene Y. C., 1971 (Box 45, Folder 1534)
          - Wang, Hui-ping, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1535)
          - Wang, Hui-ping, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1535A)
          - Wang, Ivan H. H., 1970 (Box 45, Folder 1536)
          - Wang, Janelle, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1537)
          - Wang, Li Hwei, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1538)
          - Wang, Ming-yue, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1539)
          - Wang, Tommy Chi-chung, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 1540)
          - Wang, Xue-Xin, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 1541)
          - Wanatabe, Osuke, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 1542)
          - Wei, Li, 1974, 1978-1982 (Box 45, Folder 1543)
          - Weng, T'ung-wen, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 1544)
          - Wibowo, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 1545)
          - Widja, Andeni, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1546)
          - Widja, Andeni, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1546A)
          - Wijesekera, N. D., 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1547)
          - Wikramagamage, Chandra, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1548)
          - Wohn, Duck-soo, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1549)
          - Wong, Albert, 1973, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1550)
          - Wong, Hok Pok (John), 1970 (Box 45, Folder 1551)
          - Wong, James, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1552)
          - Wong, Kuan-shut, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1553)
          - Wong, Kwok-Sing, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1554)
          - Wong, Wang Fai, 1966, 1972, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1555)
          - Wong, Yunn Chii, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1556)
          - Wongsam, Inson, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 1557)
          - Wongsdes, Sujit, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1558)
          - Woo, Grace Chia-ching, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1559)
          - Woo, Pei Leng, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1560)
          - Woo, Pei Leng, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1560A)
          - Wu, Bon-Tien, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1561)
          - Wu, Chao-Tsan, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1562)
          - Wu, Chao-Tsan, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1562A)
          - Wu, Chin-Yeh, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1563)
          - Wu, Di, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1564)
          - Wu, Ernest Ching-Ping, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1565)
          - Wu, Ernest Ching-Ping, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1565A)
          - Wu, Hao, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1566)
          - Wu, Mei-nai Maria, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1567)
          - Wu, Si-Ju, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1568)
          - Wu, Viview Siao-Huei, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1569)
        - Y, 1963, 1965-1980, 1983
          - Yabe, Makoto, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 1570)
          - Yabuki, Eiko, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 1571)
          - Yadav, Rajeshwar Singh, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1572)
          - Yadav, Rajeshwar Singh, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1572A)
            Restricted scholarly access-Confidential material
          - Yagi, Mariyo, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1573)
          - Yagnik, Vijay, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 1574)
          - Yamaguchi, Shigeaki (Box 46, Folder 1575)
          - Yamaguchi, Shingo, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1576)
          - Yamaguchi, Yasuko, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1577)
          - Yamasaki, Kazuo, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1578)
          - Yamamoto, Tamotsu, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1579)
          - Yamato, Kei, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1580)
          - Yamazaki, Masakazu, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 1581)
          - Yanagisawa, Taka, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1582)
          - Yanagita, Yaeko, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 1583)
          - Yang, Ching-tien, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1584)
          - Yang, Daniel S. P., 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 1585)
          - Yang, Eun Hee, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 1586)
          - Yang, Lily, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 1587)
          - Yang, Lucy, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1588)
          - Yang, Olivia O., 1980 (Box 46, Folder 1589)
          - Yang, Chou Jung, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1590)
          - Yang, Winston L. Y., 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1591)
          - Yang, Yoon-Jae, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 1592)
          - Yangco, Rhodora, 1970-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 1593)
          - Yano, Hideyuki, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 1594)
          - Yano, Tomaszo, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 1595)
          - Yao, Kung Wei, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1596)
          - Yap, Mong Lin, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 1597)
          - Yap, Sally S., 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1598)
          - Yapa, Pathirannehelage Jayatissa, 1965, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1599)
          - Yashiro, Akio, 1965, 1967, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1600)
          - Yasmeen, Zubaida, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1601)
          - Yatco, Oscar C., 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1602)
          - Yayanagi, Tsuyoshi, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1603)
          - Yee, Cheung, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1604)
          - Yeh, Lily, 1974, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1605)
          - Yel, Yi, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1606)
          - Yeo, Hoe Koon, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1607)
          - Yeoh, Jin Leng, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1608)
          - Yeshi, Kalsang, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 1609)
          - Yodh, Shyam, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1610)
          - Yoh, Suk-kee, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 1611)
          - Yokoi, Masako, 1966, 1976-1978 (Box 46, Folder 1612)
          - Yokoi, Shigeru, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1613)
          - Yoo, Byung-Eun, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1614)
          - Yoo, Hyun-mok, 1967, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1615)
          - Yoon, Do-kun, 1965-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1616)
          - Yorke, Shanti, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1617)
          - Yoshida, Emiko, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1618)
          - Yoshida, Minoru, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1619)
          - Yoshida, Toshio, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 1620)
          - Yoshihara, Jiro, 1965, 1967, 1969, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1621)
          - Yoshimura, Masumobu, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 1622)
          - Youasa, Takuo, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1623)
          - Young, Conrad, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1624)
          - Young, Conrad, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1624A)
          - Young, Fan, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1625)
          - Young, Ja-Lee, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1626)
          - Yu, Timothy, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 1627)
          - Yu, Wei-Su, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 1628)
          - Yuan, Shu-chen, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1629)
          - Yuhara, Kazuo, 1972, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1630)
          - Yuki, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1631)
          - Yun, Arthur Yueh, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1632)
          - Yun, Isang, 1967-1968, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1633)
          - Yutaka, Junko, 1963, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1634)
        - Z, 1970-1973, 1975, 1978, 1982-1983
          - Zayas, Cynthia Neri, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1635)
          - Zahoor, Sabahat, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1636)
          - Zaman, Arshad, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1637)
          - Zeng, Shanqing, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 1638)
          - Zheng, John Quansheng, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 1639)
          - Ziayee, M. Akbar, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1640)
          - Zulkifli, Rokiah, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 1641)
          - Zurjati, Zoebir, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1642)
      - Asian Libraries, 1966, 1969, 1974, 1977; 5
        - Asian Libraries, 1966, 1969, 1974, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 1643)
      - Asian Museums, 1961, 1963-1982, 1985; 6
        - Afghanistan, 1966, 1971-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1644)
        - Bangladesh, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 1645)
        - Bangladesh, Dacca Museum, 1968-1972, 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1646)
        - Burma, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 1647)
        - Cambodia, 1972, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1648)
        - Ceylon, 1968-1970, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1649)
        - General, 1970, 1972, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1650)
        - Hong Kong, 1968-1970, 1972, 1974, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1651)
        - India, 1964, 1968-1973, 1975-1978 (Box 48, Folder 1652)
        - India, Bal Bhavan Children's Art Centre, 1965-1966 (Box 48, Folder 1653)
        - India, Government Museum, Madras, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 1654)
        - India, Museum and Picture Gallery, Baroda, 1966, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 1655)
        - India, Museum of Art & Archaeology, 1970-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 1656)
        - India, Museums Association of India, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 1657)
        - India, National Museum, New Delhi, Agrawal, Op, 1963, 1969-1978 (Box 48, Folder 1658)
        - Indonesia, 1969-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1659)
        - Indonesia, Museum Wayang, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 1660)
        - Indonesia, National Museum, Amir Sutrarga, 1969-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1661)
        - Indonesia, Sana Budaha Museum, Jogjakarta, 1970-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1662)
        - Japan, 1961, 1966, 1971, 1973-1974, 1976-1979 (Box 48, Folder 1663)
        - Japan, Heian Museum, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 1664)
        - Japan, National Museum of Western Art, 1964, 1967-1970 (Box 48, Folder 1665)
        - Japan, Tokyo National Museum, 1969, 1971-1972, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 1666)
        - Korea, National Museum of Korea, 1970, 1973-1974, 1976-1978, 1982, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 1667)
        - Malaysia, 1966, 1968-1970, 1973, 1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1668)
        - Nepal, 1968, 1972, 1976-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1669)
        - Pakistan, 1964, 1970-1971, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 1670)
        - Philippines, Silliman University Anthropology Museum, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 1671)
        - Taipei, 1971, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 1672)
        - Thailand, 1969-1975, 1977, 1980, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 1673)
        - Vietnam, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 1674)
        - West Irian (Indonesia), 1971-1972, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 1675)
      - Asian Organizations, 1959, 1961-1980, 1982-1983; 7
        - Afghanistan (Box 49, Folder 1676)
        - Asia, 1963-1964, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1677)
        - Bangladesh, 1976-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1678)
        - Cambodia (Kampuchea), 1972-1974 (Box 49, Folder 1679)
        - China, 1965-1966, 1969-1970, 1977-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1680)
        - Hong Kong, Circle Art Group in Hong Kong, 1966-1969 (Box 49, Folder 1681)
        - India, 1964, 1966, 1968-1980, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 1682)
        - India, Centre for Art and Archaeology, Printed Matter, 1969, 1971-1973 (Box 49, Folder 1683)
        - India, Indian National Theatre, 1964, 1966-1967, 1969-1971, 1975, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 1684)
        - India, International Cultural Center, Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 50, Folder 1685)
        - India, International Cultural Center, Printed Matter, 1964-1965, 1968, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 1686)
        - India, Little Ballet Troupe, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 1687)
        - India, National Centre for the Performing Arts, Printed Matter, 1966-1969, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1688)
        - India, Yatrik, 1964-1967, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 1689)
        - Indonesia, 1968-1970, 1978, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 1690)
        - Indonesia, 1968-1970, 1978, 1980 (Box 247, Folder 4714)
        - Japan (Folder 1 of 2), 1963-1968, 1971-1974, 1976-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1691)
        - Japan (Folder 2 of 2), 1963-1968, 1971-1974, 1976-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1692)
        - Khmer, Applied Research Center for Archaeology and Fine Arts (ARCAFA), 1973-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1693)
        - Korea, 1965, 1967, 1972-1976, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 1694)
        - Korea, Seoul School of Drama & Drama Centre of Korea, 1959, 1961-1969, 1973, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 1695)
        - Malaysia, 1965-1968, 1970, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 1696)
        - Nepal, 1971-1973, 1975-1977 (Box 51, Folder 1697)
        - Pakistan, 1968, 1970-1974, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 1698)
        - Philippines, 1962, 1966-1967, 1970-1977, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 1699)
        - Philippines, Philippine Educational Theatre Association (PETA), Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 51, Folder 1700)
        - Philippines, Philippine Educational Theatre Association (PETA), Printed Matter, 1968-1974 (Box 52, Folder 1701)
        - Philippines, Philippine Educational Theatre Association (PETA), Printed Matter, 1968-1971, 1975, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 1702)
        - Singapore, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 1703)
        - Sri Lanka, 1967-1970, 1972, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1704)
        - Taipei, Taipei Performing Arts Center, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 1705)
        - Thailand, 1969-1975, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 1706)
        - Thailand, Southeast Asian Ministers of Education Secretariat (SEAMEO), 1973, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1707)
        - Tibet, Lhamo: Folk Opera Theater of Tibet, 1972, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 1708)
        - Vietnam, Vietnamese Traditional Opera, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 1709)
      - Countries, 1958-1959, 1962-1963, 1966, 1969-1975, 1977; 8
        - Afghanistan, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1710)
        - Bangladesh, 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1711)
        - Hong Kong, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1712)
        - Indonesia, 1966, 1969-1970, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1713)
        - Japan, 1958, 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 1714)
        - Korea, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 1715)
        - Malaysia, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 1716)
        - Nepal, 1966, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 1717)
        - Philippines, 1966, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 1718)
        - Sri Lanka, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 1719)
        - Thailand, 1959, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 1720)
      - International Agencies, 1962-1980; 9
        - Amnesty International, 1973, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1721)
        - Asian & Pacific Council (ASPAC), 1968, 1971-1974 (Box 54, Folder 1722)
        - International Association for Cultural Freedom, 1963, 1968, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 1723)
        - International Association of Plastic Arts, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1724)
        - International Congress of Orientalists, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 1725)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Agrawal, O. P., Mission Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 1726)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Ethical Rules of Museum Acquisition, 1969-1973 (Box 54, Folder 1727)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Hughes de Varine-Bohan Correspondence, 1967-1974, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1728)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Illicit Art Exports, Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 54, Folder 1729)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Illicit Art Exports, Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1975 (Box 54, Folder 1730)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Illicit Art Exports, Position Papers by Organizations, 1970-1974 (Box 54, Folder 1731)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Printed Materials, 1967, 1969, 1971-1973, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 1732)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morley, Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 1733)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morley, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 1734)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morley, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1735)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morley, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 1736)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morley, Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 1737)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morley, 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder 1738)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), U.S. National Committee, 1968, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 1739)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM), World Museum Fund, 1969-1970, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1740)
        - International Music Council, Printed Material, 1966, 1968, 1970-1975 (Box 56, Folder 1741)
        - International Society for Education Through Art (INSEA), 1969, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 1742)
        - International Theatre Institute, 1971-1973 (Box 56, Folder 1743)
        - Italy, Instituto Internazionale de Musica Comparata, 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 1744)
        - Mandapa Centre, 1970, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1745)
        - P. E. N., 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 1746)
        - United Nations, Fundwi, 1968-1970 (Box 56, Folder 1747)
        - United Nations, General, 1963, 1967-1969, 12972, 1975-1976, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1748)
        - United Nations, UNESCO, Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1977, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 1749)
        - United Nations, UNESCO, Printed Material (Folder 1 of 2), 1962-1964, 1967-1968, 1973-1974, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 1750)